<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BU mApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="enginfo"><![CDATA[The College of Engineering (ENG) at Boston University was established in 1950. It consists of five departments: The Department of Mechanical Engineering (ME), The Department of Biomedical Engineering (BME), The Department of Electrical & Computer Engineering (ECE), The Division of Materials Science and Engineering (MSE), and The Division of Systems Engineering (SE). The following concentrations are available: Concentration on Technology Innovation Concentration on Aerospace Engineering Concentration on Energy Technologies Concentration on Manufacturing Engineering Concentration on Nanotechnology ENG at a Glance - Top 20% of engineering schools in the US - #15 among private graduate engineering programs in the US - #12 Biomedical Engineering program - Engineering-Related Research Expenditure: $95.6 million - Faculty: 157 - Undergraduate Students: 1,662, Master’s: 288, Doctoral: 55]]></string>
    <string name="leftarrow"><![CDATA[<]]></string>
    <string name="harinfo">The Questrom School of Business, formally known as the School of Management, is the business school at Boston University. It was founded in 1913 and offers a Bachelor os Science in Business Administration (BSBA), a Master of Business Administration (MBA), a Master of Science (MS), a Master of Science in Management Studies (MSMS), and two PH.D. programs. In 2015, the school received a $50 million grant from Allen and Kristi Questrom, and the name was changed to the Questrom School of Business. The name of the building is called the Rafik B. Hariri Building, named after the former Prime Minister of Lebanon who was a BU trustee, and contains over 40 classrooms, a 375-seat lecture hall, five computer labs and a library. Available concentrations for undergraduate students are Finance, Information Systems, Accounting, Marketing, Operations and Technology Management, Entrepreneurship, General Management, International Management, Organizational Behavior and Business Law. Questrom at a glance: - Undergraduate Students: 1,748 - Postgradute students: 881 - 80+ countries represented by students and faculty - #44 Best Business Schools on US News - Male: 59.4% Female: 40.6% - Average GPA: 3.3 - 33% percent of students are international</string>
    <string name="questrom_events">QUESTROM EVENTS</string>
    <string name="college_of_arts_and_sciences_events">COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES EVENTS</string>
    <string name="casinfo"><![CDATA[The College of Arts and Sciences (CAS) at Boston University was established in 1873. It is the largest undergraduate school at Boston University. It offers a Bachelor of Arts degree in 23 different departments and 20 interdisciplinary programs. With over 2,500 courses offered, the school is split into four broad categories: natural science, social science, humanities and math & computer science. About half of the students at Boston University are enrolled through at the College of Arts and Sciences, with almost all students taking a few courses at the school during their academic career. CAS at a Glance: - Total undergraduate students: 6,777 - Total postgraduates: 1,762 - Student-Faculty Ratio: 12:1 - All CAS students are required to complete a full year of writing. - average SAT scores for incoming freshman: 1990 - Average GPA for incoming freshman: 3.65 - Population: 63% female and 37% male - Faculty: 864’ - Sponsored research: $61.4 million]]></string>
    <string name="left"><![CDATA[>]]></string>
    <string name="sarinfo"><![CDATA[The College of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, also known as Sargent College (SAR) was founded in 1881. It offers a Bachelor of Science (BS) degree for undergraduates and a Master or Science (MS) degree for graduate students. The school prepares students for clinical careers in health care and rehabilitation sciences and places a focus on comprehensive health care. There are four academic departments within the college: the Department of Health Sciences, the Department of Occupational Therapy, the Department of Physical Therapy & Athletic Training and the Department of Speech, Language & Hearing Sciences. PhD and DPT programs are also available for graduate students. SAR at a Glance: - Sargent is home to the first nationally funded psychiatric rehabilitation center in the United States - Ranked #1 by US News and World Report for its occupational therapy program at the graduate level. - Ranked #12 by US News and World Report for its speech-language pathology at the graduate level. - 110 Faculty members - 1235 Undergraduate students, 496 graduate students - 1,200 clinical sites around the US and abroad where Sargent students can apply their skills in a real world setting. - Average SAT score: 92% percentile - Average GRE score: 66% - Sargent contains a total of 35 clinical education centers and research labs and centers - Total Federal & grant funds received in 2016/2017: $15,942,117]]></string>
    <string name="sargent_college_events">SARGENT COLLEGE EVENTS</string>
    <string name="cgsinfo">The College of General Studies was founded in 1952. It is a two year, general education program thats focuses on a core curriculum. The curriculum is constructed around a team system with a limited number of students per team. All incoming freshman that are admitted into the college must complete the core curriculum in their freshman and Sophomore year and then go on to complete a degree in one of the nine other undergraduate schools at Boston University. The college offers classes in the Social Sciences, Natural Sciences, Humanities and Rhetoric. Students are not allowed to transfer into another college until after they have completed the two year program. In their Sophomore year, students are expected to complete a Capstone project where they research and present a solution to a prevalent social problem. Admission into the college is either granted through the Fall September program, or the January Boston-London Program, in which students begin in January and complete their freshman year classes with a 6 week program in London over the Summer. CGS at a Glance: - Average SAT for incoming freshman: 1785 - Average GPA for incoming freshman: 3.3 - Courses are taught by professors with Ph.D.s - Summer and Fall study abroad programs are available in London</string>
    <string name="sedinfo"><![CDATA[The Boston University School of Education was established in 1918. For undergraduates, It offers a Bachelor of Science degree in ten different programs, while graduates have the option to choose from a Master of Education degree, Master of Arts in Teaching degree, Doctor of Education Degree and a Certificate of Advanced Graduate Study. The school was ranked 45th in the nation by U.S News & World Report in 2016. It is home to the oldest continuously published journal in the field of education, called the Journal of Education, founded in 1875. It has approximately 1,086 students and 29 academic staff. Undergraduate Programs - BS in Bilingual Education - BS in Deaf Studies - BS in Early Childhood Education - BS in Elementary Education - BS in English Education - BS in Mathematics Education - BS in Modern Foreign Language Education - BS in Science Education - BS in Social Studies Education - BS in Special Education Masters Programs - Master of Arts in Teaching in English Education - Master of Arts in Teaching in Mathematics Education - Master of Arts in Teaching in Modern Foreign Language Education - Master of Arts in Teaching in Science Education - Master of Arts in Teaching in Social Studies Education - Master of Education in Applied Human Development - Master of Education in Counseling - Master of Education in Curriculum & Teaching (Online) - Master of Education in Curriculum &Teaching - Master of Education in Deaf Education -]]></string>
    <string name="lawinfo">The School of Law, established in 1872, is located at the center of Boston University’s campus. It is a nationally ranked law school, ranking 23rd in the country by “U.S. News and World Report.” Three of the specialities rank in the top ten in the nation: Health Law (#2), Tax Law (#7) and Intellectual Property Law (#9). LAW at a glance: - One of the first schools to admit people regardless of race or gender - It is the second oldest law school in the state of Massachusetts - More than 200 classes and seminars offered - 21 study abroad opportunities - 17 dual degree programs - 10.6:1 student to faculty ratio - Median GPA of graduating students: 3.65 - Median LSAT score: 163 - Ranked #1 nationally by Princeton Review for “Best Professors”</string>
    <string name="gsuinfo">The George Sherman Union (GSU) is the student union building at Boston University and Boston University Academy. The Brutalist-styled building opened in Spring 1963. When it opened, the Union had a 10-lane bowling alley in its basement. The building is named for the Boston industrialist, philanthropist, and Boston University benefactor. The Union was modeled after similar student centers in Midwestern universities.Inside are many of Boston University\'s administrative offices, a nine-restaurant food court, two bank branches, several auditoriums and other open space, as well as the BU Escort Security Service. The GSU abuts Mugar Memorial Library, the school\'s main library.Students come to the GSU to organize events, gather and exchange information, and meet people. It provides an atmosphere for study and conversation.</string>
    <string name="warreninfo">Warren Towers is one of the three Boston University dormitories traditionally intended for underclassmen, the others being The Towers and West Campus. The building is located at central campus, next to the College of Communication (COM) and across from the College of Arts and Sciences (CAS). Housing approximately 1800 students, it is the second-largest non-military dormitory in the country. The closest MBTA stop is Boston University East on the Green Line B Branch, located directly in front of B and C Towers, in a center reservation on Commonwealth Avenue.</string>
    <string name="warren_towers_dorms_info">WARREN TOWERS DORMS INFO</string>
    <string name="shsinfo"><![CDATA[SHS is the Student Health Services at Boston University. Its aim is to promote wellness, preserve health and enable academic achievement for students at BU. Any full-time BU Student, including online students, can use SHS. No student will be refuted the service due to their status or insurance. SHS is composed of 5 different services: Primary Care, Behavioral Medicine, Wellness & Prevention, Sexual Assault Response & Prevention Center, and Athletic Training. Primary Care is open everyday of the week, except for Sunday, but has a 24/7 on-call service. The Behavioral Medicine, Wellness & Prevention and Sexual Assault Response & Prevention Center are open Monday-Friday.]]></string>
</resources>
